You want to kill me,
Tang Zhiluo.
I am Luo Shuyan, the adopted daughter of the Shang family.
I am not Tang Zhiluo at all.
Then do it.
Zhiluo, Zhiluo.
It seems your appointment was not pleasant, Princess.
Are you laughing at me, Your Highness?
I wouldn't dare.
I just want to remind you, Princess Xiyao,
that you are not only Princess Consort Yu,
but also Princess Xiyao of Rouran.
You are all
sanctimonious hypocrites.
You keep talking about the greater good,
but you push the fate of the country onto me alone.
Is it to cover up your incompetence?
Instead of getting angry here, Princess,
you might as well think about how to proceed
to break free from the shackles of fate.
It's getting late.
I will take my leave.
Your Highness specifically asked for this box as part of the dowry.
It seems
I should congratulate Your Highness on getting what you wanted.
It seems the Princess has figured it out.
Your Highness is right.
How I proceed from now on is entirely up to me.
Why are you in such a hurry to reconcile with me?
Your Highness doesn't need to test me.
I sincerely want to cooperate with Your Highness.
You get the throne,
and I get my freedom.
The Princess is indeed a sensible person.
I've found out.
More than a month ago,
Shang Zaiyi bought
a dying Tang Zhiluo from human traffickers
and adopted her as his daughter.
What an adopted daughter.
She's just his killing tool.
Jingxuan, stay calm.
You care too much about Tang Zhiluo.
They seized this weakness,
trying one scheme after another.
They just want you to, after losing the Soul Jade,
lose your mind.
I understand.
Don't worry.
Jingxuan,
if you can't have both the empire and the beauty,
how will you choose?
Enough, Su Zhiye.
You can't expect everyone to be like you.
Sorry, I didn't mean that.
You're right.
Remember to take your medicine.
Although it can't completely replace the Soul Jade,
it can keep you lucid.
The postponement of the crown prince ceremony
is a good thing for us.
If we don't eliminate Prince Yu and the Shang family,
your position as the crown prince won't be secure.
Your Highness.
These are pills I specially made.
By the way, I added honey to them.
They are not bitter.
Who said I'm afraid of bitterness?
Tang Zhiluo.
Do you know?
I used to
never be afraid of bitterness.
But after meeting you,
I became cautious.
So you have to take responsibility for me.
I beg you.
Please don't leave me again.
As long as you don't leave me,
I'm willing to do anything.
Prince Shuo has caught a cold
and is not receiving guests.
Prince and Princess Yu,
please come back another day.
We came to visit our sixth brother.
Since he doesn't want to see guests,
we can come back another day.
Then please give this to our sixth brother, Mr. Su.
I thank Princess Yu on behalf of Prince Shuo.
Thank you, Mr. Su.
Su Zhiye seems unreliable,
but he is actually very cautious.
He won't give the item to Yuwen Jingxuan.
What?
Am I that naive in your eyes, Princess?
You used me as a decoy
to achieve your own goals.
Who taught you to use idioms like that?
But it's close enough.
I just put a few Gu worms
on Su Zhiye.
What Gu worms?
Don't worry, Princess.
They won't hurt Su Zhiye.
You overthink it, Your Highness.
That's not what I meant.
Don't worry, Princess.
I'm just using the Gu worms on him
to make the medicine Yuwen Jingxuan is taking
lose its effect.
Since we are allies,
listen to my advice, Princess.
If you want to live freely,
don't care too much about others.
If you want to live long,
don't leave yourself any weaknesses.
Princess, you don't need to be sad.
Although I can't be your sweetheart,
I can be your ally.
Jingxuan, Jingxuan.
Wake up, Jingxuan. Jingxuan.
How many times have I told you
not to stand behind me?
Where is Tang Zhiluo?